<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Beetle Goes Places</title>
    <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Beetle Goes Places</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://beetlegoesplaces.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Olonzac</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-olonzac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-olonzac/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned in a previous post, we went on the Beetle to a village in South of France called Olonzac. It is stated to be the capital of Minervoise. The population is around 1600.
          There are vineyards all around the village and vinery on almost all corners.
There is a peaceful park on the east part of the village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Sainte Héléne</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-sainte-helene/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-sainte-helene/</guid>
      <description>Some weeks ago we booked a one night stay at a bed and breakfast in a village named Olonzac, in southern France, that our friend recommended. We were really excited to go there on the beetle and enjoy the beautiful view that south of France has to offer. Unfortunately we had to cancel the reservation due to my health. According to the booking site were we did the reservation we had to pay 30 EUR in cancelation fee but we received an email from the owners of the B&amp;amp;B informing us that they will not charge us the cancelation fee and a hope to see us sometime in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Hospital</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-hospital/</guid>
      <description>The reason for us not traveling lately is that I have been sick. The beetle has truly been a Super beetle, getting me to and from the hospital for many days.
I have to tell you about a parking garage in Sanitas Hospital Cima. Each time we parked there we saw expensive supercars, which does not surprise me because it has the cleanest floors I have ever seen, and they are white!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Tossa</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-tossa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-tossa/</guid>
      <description>We went on a day trip on the Beetle to a small town named Tossa de Mar, Catalonia, Spain, located on the Costa Brava. It is a charming town with a beautiful fortified medieval area from the 14th century. The city centre is a little crowded and full of tourist shops selling all kind of tourist merchandise but the Vila Vella and the beaches are really worth the visit. The narrow cobblestone streets, stone walls and the vegetation is very charming and peaceful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The day it all began</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/the-day-it-all-began/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/the-day-it-all-began/</guid>
      <description>I have wanted to own a Volkswagen Beetle since I was a teenager. On the 29th of June 2017 that dream came true when my boyfriend gave me one as a birthday present.
We spent a lot of time surfing the internet and traveling around Spain in a rental car to find the right Beetle. We stumbled upon this white beautiful 1971 model of 1302 Super Beetle in Tarragona, Spain. The owner had restored this car beautifully, he had held on to the original character of the car and the engine sounded perfectly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>