<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Beetle Goes Places</title>
    <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Beetle Goes Places</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Minerve</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-minerve/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-minerve/</guid>
      <description>Minerve is one of the most charming village that I have visited. It&amp;rsquo;s history goes back to 46 BC where Minerve was a camp for the 10th Roman Legion.
Minerve was a powerful town during the medieval era where cathars lived. But in June 1210 the town was caught in the torments of the Crusade against the Albigeois. In 1209 Simon de Montfort, the military chief of the Crusade, ordered the destruction of the town by having catapults and birdtraps set up round the fortified town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Homps</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-homps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-homps/</guid>
      <description>We talked to our hosts in Sainte Helene about our itinerary and they recommended a detour to Homps to see the Canal du Midi. Seeing that Homps is only 5 minute drive from Olonzac, it made perfect sense to take the detour to see it.
Canal du Midi or the Canal of the two seas is 240 KM long and man made. It is considered to be the greatest construction work in the 17th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Carcassonne</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beelte-goes-to-carcassonne/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beelte-goes-to-carcassonne/</guid>
      <description>Carcassonne is a beautiful fortified town in south of France. The medieval fortress was added to UNESCO list of World Heritage Sites in 1997. It is now probably the most visited tourist attraction in south of France and probably also one of the top tourist attractions in the whole of France out side of Paris. The tourism is the main income stream in Carcassonne along with manufacture and wine making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Lagrasse</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-lagrasse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-lagrasse/</guid>
      <description>We were recommended by the owners of the bed and breakfast we stayed at in Olonzac to visit a village named Lagrasse. This village is part of the Les Plus Beaux Villages de France association, which means &amp;ldquo;The most beautiful village of France&amp;rdquo; and was really worth the visit.
L&amp;rsquo;Orbieu is a river that is over 84km long that divides Lagrasse. On the right side there is the village and on the left bank there is an abbey/monastery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Olonzac</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-olonzac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-olonzac/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned in a previous post, we went on the Beetle to a village in South of France called Olonzac. It is stated to be the capital of Minervoise. The population is around 1600.
          There are vineyards all around the village and vinery on almost all corners.
There is a peaceful park on the east part of the village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Sainte Helene</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-sainte-helene/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-sainte-helene/</guid>
      <description>Some weeks ago we booked a one night stay at a bed and breakfast in a village named Olonzac, in southern France, that our friend recommended. We were really excited to go there on the beetle and enjoy the beautiful view that south of France has to offer. Unfortunately we had to cancel the reservation due to my health. According to the booking site were we did the reservation we had to pay 30 EUR in cancelation fee but we received an email from the owners of the B&amp;amp;B informing us that they will not charge us the cancelation fee and a hope to see us sometime in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Hospital</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-hospital/</guid>
      <description>The reason for us not traveling lately is that I have been sick. The beetle has truly been a Super beetle, getting me to and from the hospital for many days.
I have to tell you about a parking garage in Sanitas Hospital Cima. Each time we parked there we saw expensive supercars, which does not surprise me because it has the cleanest floors I have ever seen, and they are white!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Tossa</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-tossa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-tossa/</guid>
      <description>We went on a day trip on the Beetle to a small town named Tossa de Mar, Catalonia, Spain, located on the Costa Brava. It is a charming town with a beautiful fortified medieval area from the 14th century. The city centre is a little crowded and full of tourist shops selling all kind of tourist merchandise but the Vila Vella and the beaches are really worth the visit. The narrow cobblestone streets, stone walls and the vegetation is very charming and peaceful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The day it all began</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/the-day-it-all-began/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/the-day-it-all-began/</guid>
      <description>I have wanted to own a Volkswagen Beetle since I was a teenager. On the 29th of June 2017 that dream came true when my boyfriend gave me one as a birthday present.
We spent a lot of time surfing the internet and traveling around Spain in a rental car to find the right Beetle. We stumbled upon this white beautiful 1971 model of 1302 Super Beetle in Tarragona, Spain. The owner had restored this car beautifully, he had held on to the original character of the car and the engine sounded perfectly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>