<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Beetle Goes Places</title>
    <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Beetle Goes Places</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Luxembourg</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-luxembourg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-luxembourg/</guid>
      <description>After a good weekend in nuremberg we headed to Luxembourg with a new window. We decided to stay in the country side rather than in the city.
We booked a night at a chateau in the north part of the country.
    When we arrived we were asked if we want to participate in the Gala dinner. We kind of laughed inside us since all of our better clothes had been robbed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Nuremberg, Germany</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-nuremberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-nuremberg/</guid>
      <description>In the evening of day three we went over the German border from Switzerland and headed to Stuttgard. On our way we booked a room at Hotel NH Stuttgard Airport since it had such a good review and did not cost us that much. The hotel was excellent except for the parking. We called ahead to make sure that they have secure parking available but when we came it was only secure in the sense that there was a payment gate so anyone could walk into the parking lot and start breaking windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Switzerland</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-switzerland/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-switzerland/</guid>
      <description>The third day of the road trip went into just driving as far as we could towards Nuremberg where my brother lives and where the new window was going to be delivered. We decided to go through Switzerland since that was the original plan but skip a CERN tour and Lichtenstein. The window issue had put us back one and a half day so we did not stop for pictures anywhere in Switzerland we just drove through with a small detour through Geneva city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Valence, France</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-valence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-valence/</guid>
      <description>This will be a short post since very few pictures were taken this day due to lack of motivation. As I mentioned in an earlier blog post, on the morning of our second day of the road trip, someone broke into our car by breaking a rear left window. We spent most of the day on the phone with our insurance company and Carglass. First action was to get a temporary window.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Montpellier, France</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/3-beetle-goes-to-montpellier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/3-beetle-goes-to-montpellier/</guid>
      <description>Well well well, the third stop of the first day started well, we headed of from Béziers to Montpellier. It was 78 km and it took us 1 hour and 17 minutes to get there. On our way we manage to find an interesting bed and breakfast that has really good reviews and ranks really high. We parked in front of the bead and breakfast when we arrived and the owner greeted us and gave us helpful tips regarding what restaurants we could consider as well a short scenic route around the city centre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Béziers, France</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/2-beetle-goes-to-beziers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/2-beetle-goes-to-beziers/</guid>
      <description>After a short stop in Figueres, Spain, we headed to France. We had a short break and fuelled up just outside of a town named Béziers.
    And afterwards we drove through the old centre of Béziers and managed to take some photos of the beetle with a beautiful background. In the background you see the Saint-Nazaire cathedral in gothic style from the 14th century.
The beetle just keeps on going without problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Figueres, Spain</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/1-beetle-goes-to-figueres/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/1-beetle-goes-to-figueres/</guid>
      <description>Finally the journey that we have been waiting for starts. We have stuffed the car with our belongings in Barcelona and headed towards our home country, Iceland.
We took some pictures of the beetle, ready to go, in front of our apartment building.
     And of course since we live just by the beach we had to have one of the beetle with a sea view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle passes ITV/MOT and gets an upgrade</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/mot2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/mot2017/</guid>
      <description>Last September it was time to bring the beetle to MOT inspection, or ITV as it is called in Spain. We brought it to a mechanic first go over it and I have to say that the mechanic was so happy to get this beautiful car to his garage. We had to change the suspension and while we had the suspension apart we had a look at the breaks and decided to change the break disks and break pads as well as the front wheal bearings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Narbonne</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-narbonne/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-narbonne/</guid>
      <description>Narbonne is a town in south of France with a population of around 52.000. This is a charming town with many historical buildings and sights.
The Canal de la Robine runs right through the town and the city does an excellent job keeping its surroundings so beautiful with flowerbeds all round.       We walked around the Archbishops garden, saw the Archbishops Cloister and the Archbishops Palace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Minerve</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-minerve/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-minerve/</guid>
      <description>Minerve is one of the most charming village that I have visited. It&amp;rsquo;s history goes back to 46 BC where Minerve was a camp for the 10th Roman Legion.
Minerve was a powerful town during the medieval era where cathars lived. But in June 1210 the town was caught in the torments of the Crusade against the Albigeois. In 1209 Simon de Montfort, the military chief of the Crusade, ordered the destruction of the town by having catapults and birdtraps set up round the fortified town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Homps</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-homps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-homps/</guid>
      <description>We talked to our hosts in Sainte Helene about our itinerary and they recommended a detour to Homps to see the Canal du Midi. Seeing that Homps is only 5 minute drive from Olonzac, it made perfect sense to take the detour to see it.
Canal du Midi or the Canal of the two seas is 240 KM long and man made. It is considered to be the greatest construction work in the 17th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Carcassonne</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beelte-goes-to-carcassonne/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beelte-goes-to-carcassonne/</guid>
      <description>Carcassonne is a beautiful fortified town in south of France. The medieval fortress was added to UNESCO list of World Heritage Sites in 1997. It is now probably the most visited tourist attraction in south of France and probably also one of the top tourist attractions in the whole of France out side of Paris. The tourism is the main income stream in Carcassonne along with manufacture and wine making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Lagrasse</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-lagrasse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-lagrasse/</guid>
      <description>We were recommended by the owners of the bed and breakfast we stayed at in Olonzac to visit a village named Lagrasse. This village is part of the Les Plus Beaux Villages de France association, which means &amp;ldquo;The most beautiful village of France&amp;rdquo; and was really worth the visit.
L&amp;rsquo;Orbieu is a river that is over 84km long that divides Lagrasse. On the right side there is the village and on the left bank there is an abbey/monastery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Olonzac</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-olonzac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-olonzac/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned in a previous post, we went on the Beetle to a village in South of France called Olonzac. It is stated to be the capital of Minervoise. The population is around 1600.
          There are vineyards all around the village and vinery on almost all corners.
There is a peaceful park on the east part of the village.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Sainte Helene</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-sainte-helene/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-sainte-helene/</guid>
      <description>Some weeks ago we booked a one night stay at a bed and breakfast in a village named Olonzac, in southern France, that our friend recommended. We were really excited to go there on the beetle and enjoy the beautiful view that south of France has to offer. Unfortunately we had to cancel the reservation due to my health. According to the booking site were we did the reservation we had to pay 30 EUR in cancelation fee but we received an email from the owners of the B&amp;amp;B informing us that they will not charge us the cancelation fee and a hope to see us sometime in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Hospital</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-hospital/</guid>
      <description>The reason for us not traveling lately is that I have been sick. The beetle has truly been a Super beetle, getting me to and from the hospital for many days.
I have to tell you about a parking garage in Sanitas Hospital Cima. Each time we parked there we saw expensive supercars, which does not surprise me because it has the cleanest floors I have ever seen, and they are white!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beetle Goes To Tossa</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-tossa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/beetle-goes-to-tossa/</guid>
      <description>We went on a day trip on the Beetle to a small town named Tossa de Mar, Catalonia, Spain, located on the Costa Brava. It is a charming town with a beautiful fortified medieval area from the 14th century. The city centre is a little crowded and full of tourist shops selling all kind of tourist merchandise but the Vila Vella and the beaches are really worth the visit. The narrow cobblestone streets, stone walls and the vegetation is very charming and peaceful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The day it all began</title>
      <link>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/the-day-it-all-began/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beetlegoesplaces.com/blog/the-day-it-all-began/</guid>
      <description>I have wanted to own a Volkswagen Beetle since I was a teenager. On the 29th of June 2017 that dream came true when my boyfriend gave me one as a birthday present.
We spent a lot of time surfing the internet and traveling around Spain in a rental car to find the right Beetle. We stumbled upon this white beautiful 1971 model of 1302 Super Beetle in Tarragona, Spain. The owner had restored this car beautifully, he had held on to the original character of the car and the engine sounded perfectly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>